

CONTACT



https://www.linkedin.com/in/cm 98/



christopher.mh98@gmail.com



https://github.com/CMorles98



Miranda, VE.

SKILLS

C#, JavaScript, SQL, TypeScript.

REST / SOAP / Graph QL.

ASP.NET / ASP .NET Core / Windows Forms / NodeJS / Express JS.

SSMS SQL / MYSQL / MONGO / EF Core / T-SQL / SQL SP / SSIS.

MVC / Micro Services / Hexagonal / Onion / CLEAN Architecture / CQRS.

Razor / JQuery / Angular / RxJS / ES6.

Git / GitLab / GitHub / BitBucket /
Jira / TFVC / TFC / OpenProject/
Docker

Selenium, NUnit, XUnit

LANGUAGES

Spanish- native

Written English - advanced

Spoken English - intermediate

CHRISTOPHER MORLES

SR. FULLSTACK DEV

I am a FullStack software developer with experience in reactive, functional, logical, and object-oriented programming. I excel in implementing web services (REST/SOAP) and applying design patterns such as Microservices architecture, MVC, Domain-Driven Design (DDD), CQRS, and the Repository Pattern, among others.

I have worked on the development of various web solutions, including ERPs, E-commerce, WMS, university systems, geolocation-based systems, and other types of applications. This experience provides me with a broad perspective and the ability to adapt to different development contexts.

EDUCATION

Computer engineering

In progress - Alejandro De Humboldt University 2020 - Today. Caracas, Venezuela.

EXPERIENCE

FullStack Dev: Mobeats, august 2021 - today

- Led the development of various projects, applying multiple technologies and architectures to ensure functional solutions that meet the requirements.
- Actively participated in developments with Englishspeaking native clients, facilitating effective communication and a thorough understanding of the requirements.
- Implemented unit tests to ensure code quality.
- Contributed to the continuous improvement of the development process.
- Collaborated efficiently in large teams, managing effective version control.

FullStack Dev: VE Core Systems, april 2019 - august 2021

- Developed and maintained various types of web solutions.
- Led the optimization of SQL databases and the implementation of different types of web services using Microservices and MVC.
- Collaborated efficiently in teams using GIT and TFS for effective version control.
- Conducted unit tests and automated testing with Selenium, ensuring code quality.